First, unzip the downloaded zip file and open the .blend file 00
You will see rigs and models like this one
The collections in the left outline contain the models ro oobeontrolNo End
The collections in the left outline contain the models ro oobotroNo 0 Start
The collections in the left outliner contain the models nGotrolNlt Ctae
The collections in the left outliner contain the models bQontrolN@t Oa E 0 Cta
The collections in the left outliner contain the models bQontrolN@t E 0 Cta
The collections in the left outliner contain the models nQotroNo Ctae
The collections inthe left outliner contain the models ntrolNe Endn Ctae En
The collections in the left outliner contain the models eotroNo
The collections in the left outliner contain the models E roNo C
To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode Endo
To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode F
Finpers Grasp 0.000 Snapcildofco To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode
FingersGrasp 0.000 Snapcildofco To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode
FingersGrasp 0.000 SnapChildofo To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode
Fingers Grasp 0.000 taSnapChild of.oo To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode d
FingersGrasp 0.000 taSnapChildof.o To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode 4 od
Fingers Grasp 0.000 Eesnap Child of.o To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode d
Fingers Grasp 0.000 tosnap child of.e To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode Fnd
Fingers Grasp 0.000 Snap.Child of.oo To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode Fnd
FingersGrasp 0.000 SnapChild of.oo To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode 4 Fnd
FingersGrasp 0.000 SnapChildof.o To control the rig, you need to switch to pose mode
Now you can adjust the pose HATT Fingers Grasp 0.000 LoSnapChild of..o RecetAllPose Pcke Fnd
Aot Now you can adjust the pose HAT Fingers Grasp 0.000 LSnapChild of.0 e AllPos Picke HonModi Fnd100 Sa End
Aot Now you can adjust the pose HATN FingersGrasp 0.000 LSnapChild of.0 Pck End100 AllPos Sa Fnd
Now you can adjust the pose HAP FingersGrasp 0.000 LSnapChildof.0 AllPos Picke tionMoc End100 Star Fnd
Now you can adjust the pose RotationMode
Now you can adjust the pose 4 Roonooe
Now you can adjust the pose 4 FingersGrasp 0.000 taSnapChildofo Pakoe AllPos Fod
Now you can adjust the pose 4 FingersGrasp 0.000 taSnapChildof.o >Picke End100 AllPos Fod
Now you can adjust the pose FingersGrasp 0.000 taSnapChild of.o >Picke Ed Pos Fod
Now you can adjust the pose HATN FingersGrasp 0.000 LSnapChild Of.0 AllPose >Picke onMor Fd100 S Fod
Now you can adjust the pose 4
Now you can adjust the pose
Now you can adjust the pose Fingers Grasp 0.000 TeSnapChildofoo Pc nd100 Fnd
Now you can adjust the pose Fingers.Grasp 0.000 taSnapChild of.oo AlPose Picke tonMode Fnd100 Stad End
Now you can adjust the pose Fingers.Grasp 0.000 taSnapChild of.oo Pel End100 AlPos Fod
Now you can adjust the pose HAT a Fingers.Grasp 0.000 taSnapChildof.oo eetAlPose Picke otathonMode Fnd100 Stad End
Now you can adjust the pose 4 Fingers Grasp 0.000 toSnapChildof.o Re AllPose Picke tionMoc Fnd100 Sa End
Nowyou can adjustthepose
Now you can adjust the pose
ResetAPos Don't forget to install the rig tools 3.68.12.zip included in 00 the@owr blenderaddor
esetAPos Don't forget to install the rig tools 3.68.12.zip included in the@ownloadeefilein rblenderaaddor 100
eeea Pn Don't forget to install the rig tools 3.68.12.zip includedin thedownloadeg'fileint Urbleneraddor
eeea Pn Don't forget to install the rig tools 3.68.12.zip includedin the@ownloadeefilein Urbleneeraddor
eeea Pn Don't forget to install the rig tools 3.68.12.zip included in thedownloaeeerfilei rblenderaaddor
etA en Don't forget to install the rig tools 3.68.12.zip included in thedownloaaerfilein rblen@erzaddor 100 Stat
eeetAll n Don't forget to install the rig tools 3.68.12.zip includedin the downloaeeerfilein rblen@erzaddor 100 Start
etA en Don't forget to install the rig tools 3.68.12.zip included in thedownloaaerfilein rblen@erzaddor 100 Start
Don't forget to install the rig tools 3.68.12.zip included in thedownloaderfilein rblen@erzaddor 100Start
Don't forget to install the rig tools 3.68.12.zip included in thedownloaderfilein rblen@erzaddor 100Sa
Fingers Grasp 0.000 esnapChilid ofe Don't forget to install the rig tools 3.68.12.zip included in the@downloadeerfilein rhlonderaaddor
o 3.10 120 130 40 150 e 170 29 200 210 Start 220 230 Fingers Grasp 0.000 SnapChildof eAlPose Picke PotathooMode End100 240 Star 35 Eod
o 3.10 120 130 40 150 160 170 29 200 210 Start 220 230 Fingers Grasp 0.000 SnapChildof eAlPose Picke PotathooMode End100 240 Star 35 Eod
110 210 e Fingers Grasp 0.000 SnapChild of.. ResetAllPose >Picke otationMode End100 Stad Fod
HAT工